<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CoronaStats</string>
    <string name="logoutConfirm">Are you sure you want to exit?</string>
    <string name="authenticating" translatable="false">Authenticating . . . .</string>
    <string name="translationLink" translatable="false">https://coronastats.oneskyapp.com/</string>
    <string name="noEmailClient">No email clients installed on device</string>
    <string name="sendEmailWith">Send email with..</string>
    <string name="iloveThisApp">I Love this App</string>
    <string name="thanks">Thanks for this App, it is So useful!</string>
    <string name="help_fragment">Help</string>
    <string name="about_fragment">About</string>


    <!--BoardingScreen-->
    <string name="first_slide">Social Distancing</string>
    <string name="second_slide">Wash Your Hands Often</string>
    <string name="third_slide">Wear a Face Mask</string>
    <string name="fourth_slide">Stay At Home</string>


    <!-- Description -->
    <string name="first_slide_desc">Keep your distance from others to protect them from getting sick too.</string>
    <string name="second_slide_desc">Wash your hands with soap and water, scrub your hands for at least 30 seconds.</string>
    <string name="third_slide_desc"> Consider wearing a face mask when you are sick with a cough or sneezing</string>
    <string name="forth_slide_desc">Staying at home will help control the spread of the virus to friends, the wider community.</string>

    <!-- Buttons -->
    <string name="skip">Skip</string>
    <string name="nxt_btn">Next</string>
    <string name="lets_go">Let\'s Go</string>


    <!-- ________________________________________________Privacy policy_________________________ -->


    <string name="privacy_description">
        Privacy Notice Corona-Stats\nThis privacy notice is to make it easier
        for members of the public to understand how Corona Stats may process your personal information
        during the unprecedented challenges we are all facing during the Coronavirus pandemic (COVID-19).
        \n\n
        A.   Privacy policy\n
        corona Stats is operated by a millennial. He is committed
        to protecting the privacy and security of your personal information (‘personal data’). This
        policy (together with our terms of use) describes how we collect and use your personal data
        during your use of this App, in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)
        and Associated Data Protection Legislation.
        \n\n
        B.  Processing activity
        \n
        In order for us to assist the community during this time, it is
        necessary for us to collect, hold and process personal information about you. The information
        collected and held will vary and will depend on the reason for processing. We will process
        personal information to:\n
    \n\u25CF Monitoring Covid-19 based on user usage and social care bodies and the Government
        including providing information to the public about Covid-19 and its effectiveness and
        information about capacity, medicines, equipment, supplies, services and the workforce
        within the health services and adult social care services.\n
    \n\u25CF Delivering services to patients, clinicians, the health services and adult social care
        services workforce and the public about and in connection with Covid-19, including the
        provision of information, fit notes and the provision of health care and adult social care
        services.\n
    \n\u25CF Research and planning in relation to Covid-19.\n

     Information requirements
     In regard to our processing activity, the below personal data may be processed:\n\u25CF Name \n\u25CF Email Address
        \n\n
        C.   Types of data we collect about you
        \n
        The data collected by CoronaStats App, is store, and use the following
        categories of data when you make use of this App: Device information such as android version and OS build. The app does not keep
        track of geographical location or any sort of GPS settings. Data you input into the app solely depends
        on you. sharing you data with the developer solely depends on you. The App will not restrict you from using
        it\'s services and resources.
        \n\n
        D.   Glossary
        \n
        Where we refer in this policy to your ‘personal data’, we mean any
        recorded information that is about you and from which you can be identified. It does not
        include data where your identity has been removed (anonymous data).

    Where we refer to the ‘processing’ of your personal data, we mean anything that we do with that
        information, including collection, use, storage, disclosure or retention.
        \n\n
        E.   When we Collect your data
        \n
        We will collect the vast majority of data about you when
        you give feedback about our App, e-mail or other social media functions on our App, when you
        contact the team for a problem or suggestion with our App, take careful consideration when
        sending this email and keep it formal.
        \n\n
        F.	Sharing your data with third parties
        \n
        You may share your data (Screenshots) with third parties who
        provide services sharing capabilities, the app does not keep track of this in or otherwise
        monitor this kind of actions.
        \n\n
        G.	Where we store your data
        \n
        We may store data collected within the app or electronically.
        The data is stored on our secure servers and/or in our premises within Namibia.
        \n\n
        H.	Retaining your data
        \n
        We will only retain your data for as long as we need it to
        fulfil our purposes, including any relating to legal, accounting, or reporting requirements.
        \n\n
        I.	Your rights
        \n
        Under certain circumstances, by law you have the right to:
    \n\u25CF Request access to your data (commonly known as a "subject access request"). This enables
    you to receive a copy of your data and to check that we are lawfully processing it
    \n\u25CF Request correction of your data. This enables you to ask us to correct any incomplete
    or inaccurate information we hold about you.
    \n\u25CF Request erasure of your data. This enables you to ask us to delete or remove your data
    where there is no good reason for us continuing to process it. You also have the right to ask us
        to delete or remove your data where you have exercised your right to object to processing (see below).
    \n\u25CF Object to processing of your data where we are relying on our legitimate interests
        [or those of a third party] and there is something about your particular situation which
        makes you want to object to processing on this ground.
    \n\u25CF Request the restriction of processing of your data. This enables you to ask us to suspend
        the processing of your data, for example if you want us to establish its accuracy or the reason for processing it.
    \n\u25CF Request the transfer of your data to another party.
        \n

    Depending on the circumstances and the nature of your request it may not be possible for us to
        do what you have asked, for example, where there is a statutory or contractual requirement
        for us to process your data and it would not be possible to fulfil our legal obligations if
        we were to stop.  However, where you have consented to the processing you can withdraw your
        consent at any time by emailing us at: email@address.com In this event, we will stop the
        processing as soon as we can.  However, this will not affect the lawfulness of any processing
        carried out before your withdrawal of consent and you may no longer be able to use the site
        in the same way as you did before.

    If you want to exercise any of the rights described above or are dissatisfied with the way we
        have used your information, you should contact the App developer. We will seek to deal with
        your request without undue delay, and in any event in accordance with the requirements of
        the GDPR. Please note that we may keep a record of your communications to help us resolve
        any issues which you raise.
        \n\n
        J.	Change to this policy
        \n
        Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future
        will be posted on this page.  Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to
        our privacy policy.
        \n\n



    </string>


    <!-- ________________________________________________Privacy policy End Here_________________________ -->


    //General Country details

    <string name="total_deaths">Total Deaths</string>
    <string name="total_recovered">Total Recovered</string>
    <string name="total_active">Total Active</string>
    <string name="symptoms">Symptoms</string>
    <string name="write_about_high_temperature">Write about high temperature</string>
    <string name="worldwide_cases">Coronavirus Pandemic</string>
    <string name="prevention">Prevention</string>
    <string name="treatment">Treatment</string>
    <string name="treatment_desc">There is no specific medicine to prevent or treat coronavirus disease (COVID-19). People may need supportive care to help them breathe.</string>
    <string name="self_care">Self Care</string>
    <string name="self_care_desc">If you have mild symptoms, stay at home until you have recovered. You can relieve your symptoms if you:</string>
    <string name="helpline_number">HelpLine Number</string>
    <string name="help_line">If you start showing symptoms, DO NOT go to a hospital, rather seek for help on the free hotline.</string>
    <string name="logout">Exit</string>
    <string name="app_info">App info</string>
    <string name="connect_with_me">Want to know more?</string>
    <string name="socials">Connect</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="question_need_help">Question?  Want to improve this App?</string>
    <string name="contact_owner">Feedback</string>
    <string name="_2020_2020_coronatracker">Copyright 2020 © CoronaStats</string>
    <string name="legal_info">Legal info</string>
    <string name="world_o_meters">World O meters</string>
    <string name="world_health_organisation">World Health Organisation</string>
    <string name="licence">
        —OPEN SOURCE LICENCE—
        \n
        \n
        - icons8
        \n\n
        login, password, user etc.. icon from icons8 \nhttps://icons8.com
        \n\n
        Licenced under Creative Commons Attribution-NoDerivs 3.0 Uproted
        \n\n
        https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nd/3.0/ ©Icons8 LLC
        \n\n

        <!-- _______________________________________________________________________________ -->
        - Freepik
        \n\n
        Coronavirus dark logo icon
        The full terms of the license are described in section 7 of the Freepik
        terms of use \n\n(http://www.freepik.com)
        \n\n
        Copyright © 2010 Freepik Company S.L. All rights reserved.
        <!-- _______________________________________________________________________________ -->
        \n
        \n
        - BottomNavigationViewEx
        \n
        \n
        Copyright © 2016 The BottomNavigationViewEx Project Authors (https://github.com/ittianyu/BottomNavigationViewEx)
        \n
        \n
        Licenced under MIT
        \n
        \n
        THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING
        BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND AND
        NONINFINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDER BE LABEL FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGE
        OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE
        OR USE OR OTHER DEALINGS  IN THE SOFTWARE.
        \n\n\

        <!-- _______________________________________________________________________________ -->
        <![CDATA[

        - Quicksand Font & Iconsolata Font
        \n\n
        Copyright 2011 The Quicksand Project Authors (https://github.com/andrew-paglinawan/QuicksandFamily), with Reserved Font Name
        "Quicksand".

        \n\n
        This Font Software is licenced under the SIL Open Font License, Version 1.1.\n
        This license is copied below, and is also available with a FAQ at:
        http://script.sil.org/OFL
        \n\n

        --------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
        \n
    Mobile Device Application End User License Agreement Version 1.1 - 27  August 2020
        \n

        --------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
        \n\n
        IMPORTANT – PLEASE READ CAREFULLY:
        \n\n
        This End-User License Agreement (this "Agreement") is a legal agreement between CoronaStats,
        a mobile application owned and designed by Agas Phillipus  (“CoronaStats”, “we”, “us”, or “our”)
        and you, a user (“you” or “your”) of one of our mobile application products, as further
        described below on which such product is available for download (each, an “Application” or
        “App”, and collectively, “Applications” or “Apps”).
        \n\n

        1. DESCRIPTION OF APPLICATION.  CoronaStats offered for download free of charge, certain of
        its Apps which enable you to view and analyze coronavirus statistics from across the globe.
        \n\n
        2. GRANT OF LICENSE. Provided that you have complied with, and that you continue to comply \
        with, all of the provisions of this Agreement, Corona Stats hereby grants to you a limited
        and non-exclusive right to install, run, access and use the Application in object code form
        only for the purposes described in this Agreement or otherwise as may be instructed or
        described by CoronaStats in writing.
        \n\n
        3. RESERVATION OF RIGHTS AND OWNERSHIP; THIRD PARTY CONTENT. CoronaStats reserves all rights
        related to the App which are not expressly granted to you in this Agreement. The Application
        is protected by copyright and other intellectual property laws and treaties. As between
        CoronaStats and you, CoronaStats owns all title in and to the Application, including without
        limitation all copyright and other intellectual property rights in the Application.
        You agree not to remove, conceal or otherwise modify any copyright, trademark or other
        proprietary notice or source identifier contained in or associated with the Application.
        We cannot and do not guarantee access to information or other content belonging to any third
        party which is accessible by you through the Application, or the website from which the
        App is being downloaded, or otherwise.
        \n\n
        4. USAGE RESTRICTIONS. You agree that you shall not, and that you shall not permit any other
        person, directly or indirectly, to: \n(a) sell, resell, transfer, assign, distribute, copy,
        publish, transmit, distribute, create derivative works of or otherwise disseminate, exploit
        or make available any portion or all of the Application, \n(b) reverse engineer, decompile,
        modify, translate or disassemble any portion or all of the Application including without
        limitation any of its underlying ideas, algorithms or structure, or use any portion of or
        all of the Application to create new applications, programs, products or services, \n( c )
        remove or otherwise modify any trademarks, service names, graphics, designs, logos, page
        headers, button icons, scripts, commercial markings, and trade dress appearing through the
        Application (including without limitation the trademark “CORONASTATS”) or any other Trademark
        (as hereinafter defined) which indicates that a source of goods or services are the property
        of their respective owners, or \n(d) display the name, logo, trademark or other identifier of
        any individual or entity (except for CoronaStats) in such a manner as to give the viewer the
        impression that such other individual or entity is a publisher or distributor of the Application.
        \n\n
        5. NO OTHER USE. The Application is intended solely for your personal use as described in
        this Agreement or otherwise as may be instructed or described by CoronaStats in writing.
        You may not sell, lease, charge fees for access to or any use of, the Application.
        \n\n
        6. TERMINATION.  If you fail to comply with any of the provisions of this Agreement, you may
        no longer use the Application and you shall permanently delete all copies of the Application
        from your device or which otherwise are then in your possession.

        \n\n
        7. DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTIES. YOUR USE OF THE APPLICATION IS AT YOUR OWN RISK.  THE APPLICATION
        IS PROVIDED “AS IS”, “AS AVAILABLE” AND WITH ALL FAULTS, AND CORONASTATS HEREBY DISCLAIMS ALL
        WARRANTIES, REPRESENTATIONS AND CONDITIONS, WHETHER EXPRESS, IMPLIED OR STATUTORY, INCLUDING,
        BUT NOT LIMITED TO ANY IMPLIED WARRANTIES, DUTIES OR CONDITIONS OF MERCHANTABILITY,
        NON-INFRINGEMENT, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, RELIABILITY OR AVAILABILITY, ACCURACY OR
        COMPLETENESS, QUALITY, SAFETY, SUITABILITY, WORKMANLIKE EFFORT, LACK OF VIRUSES, LACK OF
        NEGLIGENCE, OR THAT THE APPLICATION WILL PERFORM IN ANY PARTICULAR FASHION OR PRODUCE ANY
        PARTICULAR RESULT, OR OTHERWISE ARISING OUT OF OR RELATED TO THE USE OF THE APPLICATION BY
        YOU OR ANY OTHER PERSON.  CORONASTATS ALSO IS NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THE PROVISION OF ANY
        SUPPORT OR ANY OTHER SERVICES, OR THE FAILURE TO PROVIDE SUPPORT OR ANY OTHER SERVICES,
        IN CONNECTION WITH OR RELATED TO THE APPLICATION.   THERE ARE INHERENT RISKS IN THE
        DOWNLOADING AND USING OF ANY SOFTWARE, AND CORONASTATS CAUTIONS YOU TO MAKE SURE THAT YOU
        COMPLETELY UNDERSTAND THE POTENTIAL RISKS BEFORE DOWNLOADING, INSTALLING OR OTHERWISE USING
        THE APPLICATION. NEITHER CORONASTATS NOR ANY PARENT, SUBSIDIARY OR AFFILIATED ENTITY OF
        CORONASTATS, NOR ANY OF THEIR PRINCIPALS, SHAREHOLDERS, DIRECTORS, OFFICERS, MEMBERS,
        MANAGERS, LICENSORS, SUPPLIERS, EMPLOYEES, CONTRACTORS, AGENTS OR REPRESENTATIVES
        (COLLECTIVELY, THE “CORONASTATS PARTIES”) SHALL BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES THAT YOU OR ANY
        THIRD PARTY MAY SUFFER IN CONNECTION WITH OR RELATED TO YOUR DOWNLOADING, INSTALLING,
        UNINSTALLING, MODIFYING OR OTHERWISE USING THE APPLICATION.
        \n\n
        8.  LIMITATION OF LIABILITY. TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, IN NO EVENT
        SHALL CORONASTATS OR ANY OF THE OTHER CORONASTATS PARTIES BE LIABLE FOR ANY SPECIAL,
        INCIDENTAL, INDIRECT, CONSEQUENTIAL OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES WHATSOEVER, (INCLUDING WITHOUT
        LIMITATION FOR LOST PROFITS, BUSINESS OR GOODWILL, OR FOR ANY ANTICIPATED LOST PROFITS,
        BUSINESS OR GOODWILL, FOR LOSS OF CONFIDENTIAL OR OTHER INFORMATION, FOR BUSINESS
        INTERRUPTION, FOR PERSONAL INJURY, FOR LOSS OF PRIVACY, FOR FAILURE TO MEET ANY DUTY
        INCLUDING THAT OF GOOD FAITH OR OF REASONABLE CARE, FOR NEGLIGENCE, AND FOR ANY OTHER
        MONETARY OR OTHER LOSS WHATSOEVER) ARISING OUT OF OR RELATED TO YOUR USE OF THE APPLICATION
        (OR YOUR INABILITY TO USE THE APPLICATION) OR OTHERWISE IN CONNECTION WITH THIS AGREEMENT.
        THE FOREGOING SHALL APPLY WHETHER SUCH LIABILITY ARISES FROM ANY CLAIM BASED UPON CONTRACT,
        WARRANTY, TORT (INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION NEGLIGENCE), PRODUCT LIABILITY, STRICT LIABILITY,
        FAULT, BREACH OF WARRANTY, BREACH OF CONTRACT OR OTHERWISE, EVEN IF CORONASTATS OR ANY OF THE
        OTHER RUSTYBRICK PARTIES HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.  NOTWITHSTANDING
        ANY DAMAGES THAT YOU MIGHT INCUR FOR ANY REASON WHATSOEVER INVOLVING THE APPLICATION
        (INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, ANY OF THE DAMAGES REFERENCED HEREIN), THE ENTIRE LIABILITY
        OF THE CORONASTATS PARTIES COLLECTIVELY, AND YOUR EXCLUSIVE REMEDY HEREUNDER, SHALL BE LIMITED
        TO ONE THOUSAND DOLLARS ($1,000) IF YOU ARE PAYING CORONASTATS FOR USE OF THE APP, OR ONE HUNDRED
        DOLLARS ($100) IF YOU ARE USING THE APP FREE OF CHARGE. THIS LIMITATION OF LIABILITY PROVISION IS
        INTENDED TO APPLY WITHOUT REGARD TO WHETHER OTHER PROVISIONS OF THIS AGREEMENT HAVE PROVEN
        INEFFECTIVE.
        \n\n
        9.  INDEMNITY.  You shall indemnify, defend and hold CoronaStats and each of the other
        CoronaStats Parties harmless from and against any and all threatened or actual claims,
        actions, suits and demands and any and all resulting losses, liabilities, damages, expenses
        and costs, including without limitation reasonable attorneys’ fees and disbursements, which
        arise in connection with or which are related to \n(a) your breach of this Agreement, including
        without limitation your use of the Application in any manner not expressly permitted hereunder, or
        \n(b) your negligence or misconduct, or \n( c) your violation of any law or regulation.
        \n\n
        10.  PRIVACY.  CoronaStats views the protection of your privacy as an important responsibility.
        The terms regulating the handling of personally identifiable information (“PII”) and other
        information submitted by you in connection with the App is described in the CoronaStats
        App privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”) located in the settings screen.  By using the App,
        you consent to the collection and use by us of your PII as well as all other information as
        described in the Privacy Policy.
        \n\n
        11.  GOVERNING LAW; ARBITRATION; NO CLASS CLAIMS; TIMELY FILING OF CLAIMS.  This Agreement
        shall be governed and construed in accordance with the COPYRIGHT AND NEIGHBOURING RIGHTS
        PROTECTION Act No.6, of 1994. The act states: To provide for the protection of copyright and
        performers’ rights, and to provide for the matter’s incidental thereto.  Any dispute arising
        out of or relating to your use of the Application or otherwise related to this Agreement,
        including without limitation regarding any breach hereunder, shall be brought forth to
        “judicial proceedings”. This means proceedings before a court, tribunal or person having by
        law power to hear, receive and examine evidence on oath or affirmation. You shall pay for
        your own legal costs and expenses involved in any such arbitration, including without limitation
        reasonable attorneys’ fees, and we shall pay for all of our such costs and expenses unless the
        matter being arbitrated involves your breach of any of the provisions of this Agreement, in
        which case you shall pay both for your as well as for our legal costs and expenses including
        without limitation reasonable attorneys’ fees incurred by us in pursuing such a claim.  NO
        ARBITRATION OR CLAIM UNDER THIS AGREEMENT SHALL BE JOINED TO ANY OTHER ARBITRATION OR CLAIM,
        AND NO CLASS ARBITRATION PROCEEDINGS SHALL BE PERMITTED. YOU AGREE THAT REGARDLESS OF ANY
        STATUTE OR LAW TO THE CONTRARY, ANY CLAIM, SUIT OR ACTION THAT YOU MAY HAVE AGAINST ANY OF
        THE COVIDSTATS PARTIES ARISING UNDER OR RELATED TO THIS AGREEMENT MUST BE BROUGHT BY YOU
        PURSUANT TO THIS SECTION AND WITHIN ONE (1) YEAR AFTER THE DATE ON WHICH THE EVENT UNDERLYING
        SUCH CLAIM OCCURRED OR IS ALLEGED TO HAVE OCCURRED.
        \n\n
        12. MISCELLANEOUS. This Agreement and any written instructions related to the App which are
        provided by CoronaStats constitute the entire agreement between you and CoronaStats relating
        to the Application, and they supersede all prior or contemporaneous oral or written communications,
        proposals and representations with respect to the Application or any other subject matter
        covered by this Agreement. To the extent the terms of any CoronaStats policies or programs
        conflict with the terms of this Agreement, the terms of this Agreement shall control. If any
        provision of this Agreement is held to be void, invalid, unenforceable or illegal, such
        provision shall be modified by the arbitrator to most closely resemble the intent of
        CoronaStats and all other provisions of this Agreement shall continue in full force and effect.
        The failure of CoronaStats at any time to require performance by you of any provision of this
        Agreement shall in no way affect CoronaStats’ right to enforce such provisions, nor shall the
        waiver by CoronaStats of any breach of any provision of this Agreement be taken or held to
        be a waiver of any further breach of the same provision.







    ]]></string>
    <string name="take_vit">Take your Vitamins</string>
    <string name="rest_sleep">Rest and sleep</string>
    <string name="keep_warm">Keep Warm</string>
    <string name="drink_liquids">Drink plenty of liquids</string>
    <string name="take_hot">Take hot shower to ease of a soar throat and cough</string>

    <string name="hand_wash">Wash your hands often</string>
    <string name="wear_mask">Wear a face mask</string>
    <string name="avoid_sick">Avoid contact with sick people</string>
    <string name="cover_your">Cover your cough or sneeze</string>
    <string name="avoid_fly">Avoid flying to areas affected with COVID19</string>
    <string name="keep_distance">Keep a distance of 1 meter between you and others</string>
    <string name="sanitizer">Use sanitizers to reduce risk of infection</string>
    <string name="wet_wipe">Clean Surfaces and objects regularly</string>
    <string name="staircase">Staircase</string>
    <string name="elevator">Elevator buttons</string>
    <string name="gadgets">Gadgets</string>
    <string name="contaminated">Contaminated food</string>
    <string name="money">Money</string>
    <string name="public_transport">Public transport</string>


    <string name="high_fever">HIGH FEVER</string>
    <string name="sore_throat">SORE THROAT</string>
    <string name="dry_cough">DRY COUGH</string>
    <string name="tiredness">TIREDNESS</string>
    <string name="difficulty_breath">DIFFICULTY BREATHING</string>

    <string name="temper">Temperatures above 37°c</string>
    <string name="irritation_throat">Irritation in the throat</string>
    <string name="a_dry_coug">A dry cough</string>
    <string name="feeling_tired">Constantly feeling tired</string>
    <string name="difficulty_brea">difficulty breathing or Shortness of breath</string>


    <string name="protect_yourself">How to Protect Yourself &amp; Others</string>
    <string name="help_translate">Help translate CoronaStats into your language!</string>
    <string name="total_cases">Total Cases</string>
    <string name="new_cases">New Cases</string>
    <string name="new_deaths">New Deaths</string>
    <string name="total_critical">Total Critical</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="useful_links">More on COVID19</string>
    <string name="coronastats_on_twitter">CoronaStats on Twitter</string>
    <string name="coronastats_on_facebook">CoronaStats on Facebook</string>
    <string name="center_for_disease_ncontrol_and_prevention">Center for Disease\nControl and Prevention</string>
    <string name="device_info">Device info</string>
    <string name="textview">TextView</string>
    <string name="how_does_the_virus_spreads">How does the virus spreads?</string>


    <!-- These will be the helpLine Number Details for each country -->

    <!-- _______________________ Angola Hot line Details ________________________ -->
    <string name="ang_CountryCode" translatable="false">Ang</string>
    <string name="ang_helpNumber" translatable="false">111</string>

    <!-- _______________________ Botswana Hot line Details ________________________ -->
    <string name="bot_CountryCode" translatable="false">bot</string>
    <string name="bot_helpNumber" translatable="false">+267 3632273</string>
    <string name="bot1_CountryCode" translatable="false">bot</string>
    <string name="bot1_helpNumber" translatable="false">+267 3632756</string>
    <string name="bot2_CountryCode" translatable="false">bot</string>
    <string name="bot2_helpNumber" translatable="false">+267 3632757</string>
    <string name="bot3_CountryCode" translatable="false">bot</string>
    <string name="bot3_helpNumber" translatable="false">+267 3632206</string>

    <!-- _______________________ Comoros Hot line Details ________________________ -->
    <string name="com_CountryCode" translatable="false">Com</string>
    <string name="com_helpNumber" translatable="false">+269 4693641</string>
    <string name="com1_CountryCode" translatable="false">Com</string>
    <string name="com2_CountryCode" translatable="false">Com</string>
    <string name="com2_helpNumber" translatable="false">+269 4693642</string>
    <string name="com3_CountryCode" translatable="false">Com</string>
    <string name="com3_helpNumber" translatable="false">+269 4693644</string>

    <!-- _______________________ drc Hot line Details ________________________ -->
    <string name="drc_CountryCode" translatable="false">drc</string>
    <string name="drc_helpNumber" translatable="false">+243 854463582</string>
    <string name="drc1_CountryCode" translatable="false">drc</string>
    <string name="drc1_helpNumber" translatable="false">+243 841363267</string>

    <!-- _______________________ Eswatini Hot line Details ________________________ -->
    <string name="esw_CountryCode" translatable="false">esw</string>
    <string name="esw_helpNumber" translatable="false">977</string>

    <!-- _______________________ Lesotho Hot line Details ________________________ -->
    <string name="les_CountryCode" translatable="false">les</string>
    <string name="les_helpNumber" translatable="false">+266 58862893</string>

    <!-- _______________________ Madagascar Hot line Details ________________________ -->
    <string name="mad_CountryCode" translatable="false">Mad</string>
    <string name="mad_helpNumber" translatable="false">910</string>

    <!-- _______________________ Malawi Hot line Details ________________________ -->
    <string name="mal_CountryCode" translatable="false">Mal</string>
    <string name="mal_helpNumber" translatable="false">+265 887371288</string>


    <!-- _______________________ Mauritius Hot line Details ________________________ -->
    <string name="mau_CountryCode" translatable="false">Mau</string>
    <string name="mau_helpNumber" translatable="false">8924</string>

    <!-- _______________________ Mozamb Hot line Details ________________________ -->
    <string name="moz_CountryCode" translatable="false">Moz</string>
    <string name="moz_helpNumber" translatable="false">84146</string>
    <string name="moz1_CountryCode" translatable="false">Moz</string>
    <string name="moz1_helpNumber" translatable="false">82149</string>
    <string name="moz2_CountryCode" translatable="false">Moz</string>
    <string name="moz2_helpNumber" translatable="false">1490</string>
    <string name="moz3_CountryCode" translatable="false">Moz</string>
    <string name="moz3_helpNumber" translatable="false">258</string>
    <string name="moz4_CountryCode" translatable="false">Moz</string>
    <string name="moz4_helpNumber" translatable="false">*660#</string>


    <!-- _______________________ Namibia Hot line Details ________________________ -->
    <string name="nam_CountryCode" translatable="false">Nam</string>
    <string name="nam_helpNumber" translatable="false">0800100100</string>

    <!-- _______________________ Seychelles Hot line Details ________________________ -->
    <string name="sey_CountryCode" translatable="false">Sey</string>
    <string name="sey_helpNumber" translatable="false">141</string>


    <!-- _______________________ South Africa Hot line Details ________________________ -->
    <string name="rsa_CountryCode" translatable="false">RSA</string>
    <string name="rsa_helpNumber" translatable="false">0800029999</string>
    <string name="rsa1_CountryCode" translatable="false">RSA</string>
    <string name="rsa1_helpNumber" translatable="false">0800111131</string>

    <!-- _______________________ Tanzania Hot line Details ________________________ -->
    <string name="tan_CountryCode" translatable="false">Tan</string>
    <string name="tan_helpNumber" translatable="false">+255 800110124</string>
    <string name="tan1_CountryCode" translatable="false">Tan</string>
    <string name="tan1_helpNumber" translatable="false">+255 800110125</string>
    <string name="tan2_CountryCode" translatable="false">Tan</string>
    <string name="tan2_helpNumber" translatable="false">25577369919</string>

    <!-- _______________________ Zambia Hot line Details ________________________ -->
    <string name="zam_CountryCode" translatable="false">Zam</string>
    <string name="zam_helpNumber" translatable="false">909</string>
    <string name="zam1_CountryCode" translatable="false">Zam</string>
    <string name="zam1_helpNumber" translatable="false">+260 974493553</string>
    <string name="zam2_CountryCode" translatable="false">Zam</string>
    <string name="zam2_helpNumber" translatable="false">+260 964638726</string>
    <string name="zam3_CountryCode" translatable="false">Zam</string>
    <string name="zam3_helpNumber" translatable="false">+260 953898941</string>


    <!-- _______________________ Zimbabwe Hot line Details ________________________ -->
    <string name="zim_CountryCode" translatable="false">Zim</string>
    <string name="zim_helpNumber" translatable="false">+263714734593</string>
    <string name="zim1_CountryCode" translatable="false">Zim</string>
    <string name="zim1_helpNumber" translatable="false">+263774112531</string>


    <string name="coronavirus_disease">2019 Coronavirus Disease (COVID-19)</string>
    <string name="coronaviruses_cov_are">Coronaviruses (CoV) are a large family of viruses that cause illness ranging from the common cold to more severe diseases such as Middle East Respiratory Syndrome (MERS-CoV) and Severe Acute Respiratory Syndrome (SARS-CoV). A novel coronavirus (nCoV) is a new strain that has not been previously identiﬁed in humans.</string>
    <string name="visit_http">Visit  https://coronastats.oneskyapp.com/</string>
    <string name="app_version" translatable="false">Version 1.1.0</string>
    <string name="licenses">licenses</string>


</resources>